

# Rabee AL jaramani – WEB DEVELOPER

Mobile: (+971) 567657124

Date of birth: 17-04-1988

Email Address: rabeealjaramani@yahoo.com

My Portfolio: https://rabeeportfolio.herokuapp.com/

Address: Dubai (United Arab Emirates)

**Nationality:** Syrian

Languages: Arabic, English

# My Projects:

(O)

E-commerce website: <a href="https://e-star-x.herokuapp.com/">https://e-star-x.herokuapp.com/</a>

Construction company: https://construction--company.herokuapp.com/

# **ABOUT ME**

First-rate Informatics Engineer with +9 years of experience offering outstanding support to users and companies of various levels in different countries. Passionate about web development and seeking to grow in the role of a web developer by using my React, HTML and CSS skills to deliver coding excellence. Ambitious problem solver with a passion for online businesses and would like to join a team of likeminded developers. Constantly striving to improve myself and enhance my skills in technologies.

## **SKILL SET**

- Web Programming & Design: JavaScript, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, XML, React js, Redux, C#, C++, ASP.net mvc.
- Database Tools: MongoDB and Microsoft SQL.
- High knowledge in programming languages and networking.
- · Self-learning.
- Operating systems: Windows (XP, 7, 8, 10), Microsoft Windows Server (2003, 2008, 2016), Mac OS, Android, iOS, Office Tools: Microsoft Office (2003, 2007, 2013, 2016, 2019) Access, Power Point, Word, Excel.
- Computer devices, tablets, mobile phones, servers and networks.
- Security cameras CCTV and IP cameras.
- Teaching programming courses, information technology topics and computer usage.
- Build meeting and class rooms for schools and universities (projectors, mirroring, smart boards
- Data management.
- Quality assurance for applications and devices.
- Projects Management and IT planning to achieve the needs.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Information Technology Support Engineer

Diamond Island for Office Equipment [ 02/01/2020 – Current ]

City: Dubai

Country: United Arab Emirates

- Developing a new system to enhance the work flow between employees and customers.
- Web developer.
- Testing Accounting system and report bugs.
- Hardware and software maintenance.
- Troubleshooting and problem solving.

# Information Technology Engineer

**Star Computer Company**[ 15/09/2013 - 10/11/2019 ]

City: Beirut

Country: Lebanon

- Build a database for the company's goods and our customers' details.
- Tracking all tasks and orders.
- Developing Desktop applications on demands.
- Software and hardware maintenance for laptops, desktop computers, tablets, tablet pc's and iPad services.
- Install and maintain networks, terminals and internet access points.
- · Data backup.
- Recover lost or deleted data.
- Security cameras (CCTV and IP cameras) with online access.
- Testing new devices and solve any problems if existed.
- · Customer service.
- Contact with our suppliers in china to make enhancements on the devices.

#### Teacher

**Toyour Aljanna School**[ 01/08/2011 – 01/11/2011]

City: Damascus Country: Syria

> Teaching kids the computer usage and learn them to use the computer as a useful machine for learning goals.

#### **Teacher**

**Com2Net Institute**[ 01/08/2011 – 01/11/2011 ]

City: Damascus
Country: Syria

- Teaching ICDL course.
- Teaching ASP.net and C# programming for designing websites.

#### Computer technician

**IT for computers** [ 01/08/2008 – 01/11/2010 ]

City: Damascus
Country: Syria

- · Installation operating system and programs.
- Assemble Desktop computers.
- Fixing any software or hardware problems.
- · Customer service.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

# Bachelor degree of Informatics Engineering.

**Arab International University (AIU)** [15/09/2006 – 15/08/2011]

Address: Daraa Ghabaghib, Damascus (Syria)

https://www.aiu.edu.sy/